What would you say is the biggest
challenge that you ever faced throughout your career,
and how did you overcome that?
Probably one of the biggest challenges
I had was I was very young,
and Bank of America had a problem,
and they were losing several million dollars
over some period of time, minutes, hours,
because the funds transfer system had fallen down.
And they put me on an airplane,
sent me down there, and I was actually
patched these computers together to
bring funds transfer back up.
So with the amount of people and the amount
of money and the amount of scrutiny on that,
that's where I figured out, you
know what, I can actually do this.